

- +63 961 449 9827
- kgonzales1193@gmail.com
- www.keiprojects.com

  www.k
- Toril District, Davao City, Davao del Sur 8000

#### **EDUCATION**

BS Information Technology University of Negros Occideltal-Recoletos 2013 - 2014

BS Information Technology Carlos Hilado Memorial State college 2011 - 2012

### **EXPERTISE**

Web Design

Virtual Assistance

Customer Service

# **KEVIN PAUL GONZALES**

#### **ABOUT ME**

Quality Assurance Analyst with 3+ years experience who specializes in making thorough business decisions and leading others through day-to-day operations to achieve excellence. Decided to transition to Web Development and joined a coding bootcamp to continue my passion in Tech Industry. I am now seeking for a job where I can share my knowledge and skills that I have learned throughout the years with enthusiasm.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

September 2023 - March 2024

BALUARTECH SOLUTIONS

#### Fullstack Web Developer

Participated in building POS and Inventory System for a Hardware and Drug store. The system was built with Laravel and Vue JS. My daily tasks includes:

- Update UI design
- Adding new functions and features to the system.
- Revising existing codes.

Jan 2022 - March 2023

**6** EATAGAYLO

## Junior Web Developer

Participated in building web and mobile application for EATAGAYLO Food Delivery Services (eatagaylo.com), fixing bugs and minor web maintenance.

Nov 2021 - April 2021

Virtual Assistant

## Jennifer DeVinney

- Transaction Coordinator Prepare Buyer/Seller Contract
- Social Media Manager Create posts for listings and recent closed listings and daily marketing posts.
- General Admin Manage KW Command's data base.
- LMS Create listing.
- SEO optimizing agent's website
- Lead Generation extract leads from the website and call leads for possible clients.

OCT 2017 - NOV 2020 CNM BPO Solutions

# Quality Assurance Analyst

My weekly task was to audit 2-3 calls minimum of 80 calls for the 2 teams assigned to me with 15-20 head counts per team.

#### **REFERENCES**

Mary Annn Oro
CNM / SUPERVISOR

Phone: +639958708896

PETER JAKE MIRANDA
Baluartech Solutions/ CEO

Phone: 09488005645

Email: peterjakemiranda@gmail.com